Morgan Grey

Consultant



Qualifications

PRINCE2 foundation, Axelos Global – 2019

BSc Chemistry with Forensic Science and Toxicology, University of Hull - 2012

Cloud Platforms

GCP, AWS

Programming Languages

HTML, SQL, Javascript, Python, VB

IDE's

Pycharm, Atom

Operating Systems

Windows, Linux (Ubuntu)

DevOps Technologies

Git, Jenkins, Docker

Database Technologies

MySQL, Oracle SQL

Other

Agile, Prince2, Windows office suite (specialising in Excel), google suite

Consultant Profile



PROFILE

An experienced business analyst and project manager with experience in the legal and IT sectors. Expert in creating simple solutions for complex problems. I have 10 years' experience managing small teams, combining strong leadership, adaptable communication methods and formal performance management to consistently achieve 'on time' delivery of projects and services. 5 years' experience of PRINCE2 project management. Data warehouse design & management, and systems migration, including updating databases for the environment agency, Wales.

WORK EXPERIENCE - QA

CODE - https://github.com/GreyProgramming

Academy Experience

Current academy experience: creation of an LGBT website using flask, python, HTML coding and SQL integration. I am currently expanding it for SFIA2 which will integrate Docker and Ansible.

WORK EXPERIENCE - OTHER

Legal Project Manager - Hassnet LTD (Jun 2005 - Present)

Skills: Legal document and evidence management - Database admin - Data analysis

Worked directly with solicitors and barristers on development and processing of caseloads, including identifying and executing firm process improvement projects, developing tools, resources and technology including knowledge databases and forms and collaborating on development of client-level and matter-level progress reports. This enabled the firms to be more streamlined, directing their resources to areas where they would be most effective and saving time and money.

With sweeping changes to CJS funding; the number of different clients with differing needs, budgets, resources, etc, I can't accurately estimate how much time and money has been saved through implementation of these projects.

Project Manager - Polyday CIO (Jun 2015 - Present)

Project management of annual event focused on relationship and personal skills. Turned event around to making profit within 1 year. Reputation as largest event in Europe catering to the poly community, and monthly events run on meetup. https://www.meetup.com/polylondon/ and http://www.polyday.org.uk/

Project Manager – Doogri Institute and Centre of Excellence (Jun 2019 – Jan 2020)

Liaising between the director and staff, clients and suppliers to ensure that project milestones are met in a project that generates new data to completely revamp teaching methods for autistic children.

Systems & Business Analyst – Somerset Passenger Solutions & EDF Hinkley Point C (Mar 2016–Oct 2018)

Skills: Database design, development and administration, BI administration, Data analysis, Team management, Data modelling, Cost analysis, Excel, KPIs and SQL

- Managed the site inductions, project managed system and data warehouse design and implementation. MI from system used to identify time savings between stakeholders.
- Managed a project which involved tracking fly parking and updating existing records. Reported on the new requirements resulting in a QR code system with fully automate access by 2020.
- Managed a specialist service of 5 drivers who worked on a rota based on the times
 of high tide, considering both EU and domestic law. I created a new system for this
 service, which hit all the targets and was worth an additional £150K p/a to the
 company.